Guide to the Llewelyn Davies Family Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Llewelyn Davies family papers
1842-1963
GEN MSS 554
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
6.91
(12 boxes)
The Llewelyn Davies family papers contain correspondence, photographs, and other material relating chiefly to the Llewelyn Davies family, though materials also relate to members of the Du Maurier family and to author and dramatist J. M. Barrie, whose character, "Peter Pan," was inspired by the Llewelyn Davies children.
Llewelyn Davies family
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Llewelyn Davies Family Papers, formerly in the collection of Andrew Birkin, were acquired through purchase from Sotheby's, London, on the Edwin J. Beinecke Book Fund, 2004.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Box 11: Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
Associated Materials
Related material can be found in the J. M. Barrie Collection, located at the Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, and the Du Maurier Family Papers, 1818-1988, located at the University of Exeter.
LLEWELYN DAVIES FAMILY
The following chart provides lines of descent for the Llewelyn Davies family.
John Llewelyn Davies (1826-1916) m. (1859) Mary Crompton (d. 1885)
--Crompton Llewlyn Davies
--Harry Llewelyn Davies
--Theodore Llewelyn Davies
--Margaret Llewelyn Davies (1861-)
--Maurice Llewelyn Davies
--Arthur Llewelyn Davies (d. 1907) m. (1892) Sylvia du Maurier (1867-1910)
----George Llewelyn Davies (1893-1915)
----John ("Jack") Llewelyn Davies (1894-1959) m. Geraldine ("Gerrie") Gibb
----Peter Llewelyn Davies (1897-1960)
----Michael Llewelyn Davies (1900-1921)
----Nicholas Llewelyn Davies (1901-1980)
DU MAURIER FAMILY
The following chart provides lines of descent for the Du Maurier family.
George Louis Palmella Busson du Maurier (1834-1896) m. (1863?) Emma Wightwick
--Guy du Maurier (1865-1915)
--Sylvia du Maurier (1867-1910)
--Gerald du Maurier (1873-1934)
----Daphne du Maurier (1907-1989)
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTES
Arthur Llewelyn Davies (d. 1907) was one of seven children and the second son of Mary Crompton (d. 1885) and John Llewelyn Davies (1826-1916). John, a respected scholar, theologian, and translator, and outspoken advocate of worker's rights, trade unionism, and women's suffrage, was Rector at Kirby Lonsdale, Cumbria. Arthur Llewelyn Davies was admitted to the bar in 1891, and in 1892 married Sylvia du Maurier (1867-1910), daughter of illustrator and novelist George du Maurier (1834-1896). Arthur and Sylvia had five sons: George (1893-1915), John or "Jack" (1894-1959), Peter (1897-1960), Michael (1900-1921), and Nicholas (1901-1980).
Author and dramatist J. M. Barrie (1860-1937) befriended the Llewelyn Davies family in the 1890s, and his famous character "Peter Pan" was inspired by the Llewelyn Davies children. Summary information on J. M. Barrie is available in the standard print and online resources. For additional information on Barrie's relationship with the Llewelyn Davies family, see Andrew Birkin's J. M. Barrie & the Lost Boys.
Scope and Contents
The Llewelyn Davies Family Papers contain correspondence, photographs, and other material relating chiefly to members of the Llewelyn Davies family, though materials also relate to members of the Du Maurier family and to author and dramatist J. M. Barrie. The collection spans the years 1842 to 1963, with the bulk of the collection dating from 1890 to 1920.
The collection is housed in eleven boxes and organized into three series: Correspondence, Photographs, and Other Material. Boxes 9-10 contain Oversize material and box 11 contains Restricted Fragile Papers.
Series I, Correspondence, housed in boxes 1-4, is organized into four subseries: Outgoing Llewelyn Davies Family Correspondence, Incoming Llewelyn Davies Family Correspondence, Third Party Correspondence, and Llewelyn Davies Family Correspondence Compiled by Peter Llewelyn Davies.
The Outgoing Llewelyn Davis Family Correspondence subseries contains the outgoing letters of members of the Llewelyn Davies family, including Arthur Llewelyn Davies' wife Sylvia du Maurier. There are letters from Arthur and Sylvia Llewelyn Davies, and from Arthur's many siblings, but these papers feature the correspondence from Arthur and Sylvia's five sons: George, John ("Jack"), Peter, Michael, and Nicholas ("Nico"). There are letters from the boys to their parents and other relatives, to their nanny, Mary Hodgson, and to family friend J. M. Barrie ("Uncle Jim"), whose famous character, "Peter Pan," was inspired by the Llewelyn Davies children. The largest files exist for correspondence from Nicholas and Peter Llewelyn Davies to Barrie and Hodgson. There are, for example, 22 ALS from Nicholas to Barrie, dating from 1911, when Nicholas was only eight years old, to 1924, when he was a student at Oxford. There are 35 ALS from Peter to Barrie, with all but one letter dating from late 1915 to 1918, and most written during the summer and fall of 1916 when Peter was posted at the front, in France, with the 1st Battalion. Letters describe the conditions and experience of the war.
The Incoming Llewelyn Davies Family Correspondence contains letters to members of the Llewelyn Davies family from people outside the immediate family. Correspondents include Barrie, Hodgson, members of the Du Maurier family, and friends. The correspondence from Barrie includes two letters to George Llewelyn Davies, who served at the front with the 4th Battalion, only days before George's death in March 1915. Two long letters from novelist Daphne du Maurier to Nicholas Llewelyn Davies, dating from 1960 and 1963 respectively, respond to Peter's death and to what is described as a three-volume manuscript on the Llewelyn Davies family. Quite possibly she refers to Peter's compilation of family letters and papers (known as the "Morgue") noted below. In addition, there are letters from Sylvia's father, novelist George du Maurier, Henry James, Eton housemaster Hugh Macnaghten, Roger Senhouse, and others.
The Third Party Correspondence subseries includes letters between others, with additional letters from Barrie and members of the Du Maurier family.
Letters in the first three subseries are arranged alphabetically first by correspondent and then by recipient. When multiple letters are present for a particular recipient, letters are arranged chronologically.
Peter Llewelyn Davies compiled family correspondence and papers, and there is a bound volume of handwritten transcriptions of selected letters in the archive, corrected and with extensive notes, and five folders of typescript copies. The compilation, entitled "Some Davies Letters & Papers continued, 1889-1907," includes letters from Llewelyn Davies and Du Maurier family members, among others. In his J. M. Barrie and the Lost Boys (1979), Andrew Birkin cites Peter's "Some Davies Letters and Papers, 1974-1915" as a six-volume compilation. The differences between the titles and dates suggest that the volume here is a middle volume in this larger project.
Series II, Photographs, housed in boxes 5-7, is organized into four subseries: Indexes and Albums, People, Places, and Other Subjects.
The photographs in the collection were accompanied by two indexes and two. The indexes provide additional descriptive context to the actual photographs listed in the People, Places, and Other Subjects subseries. The albums, one of which includes captions and the other a signature, have been retained and housed in oversize storage.
The photographs in the People subseries are subdivided into three groups: Llewelyn Davies Family, Llewelyn Davies Family with J. M. Barrie and Others, and Others. Photographs of the Llewelyn Davies children, their parents, other members of the Du Maurier family, and J. M. Barrie date from 1870 to 1937, with the bulk dating from 1890 to 1920, when the boys where still young, and before the deaths of George and Michael in 1915 and 1921 respectively. There are studio portraits and snapshots of Sylvia and the boys, and the eight folders of family photographs, in which two or more members of the family are present, document various domestic scenes and leisure activities: excursions to the beach and fishing, vacations, and games such as cricket and tennis. There are also studio portraits of several members of the Du Maurier family.
Photographs in the Llewelyn Davies Family with J. M. Barrie and Others subseries include images of Barrie, Bernard Shaw, Dora Carrington, and groups of people. Other photographs include images of the Llewelyn Davies' homes and retreats, including the Kirby Lonsdale vicarage and the Black Lake cottage in Surrey, a short walk from the Barrie's country home, where the Llewelyn Davies vacationed in the summer of 1901.
There are approximately 435 photographs in the collection, providing a broad and intimate resource into the lives of J. M. Barrie and the Llewelyn Davies and Du Maurier families. Many photographic portraits in the collection were taken by well-known photographers or at well-known studios, including Frederick Hollyer, H. S. Mendelssohn, and Lizzie Caswall Smith. When photographers or studios are known, attributions are made in folder notes in the box list. The photographs are accompanied by numeric and chronological indexes that provide additional item-level description, including the names of individuals and groups, places, and dates.
Series III, Other Material, housed in box 8, is organized into four subseries: Drawings, Printed Ephemera, Writings and Notes, and Other Material. Materials include the following: drawings of Sylvia and Arthur Llewelyn Davies by Guy du Maurier; holograph draft and draft fragments of writings by J. M. Barrie; two printed albums, My Confession Book and The Querist's Album, completed in manuscript by various members of the Llewelyn Davies family and friends, including Barrie, sometimes with revealing and amusing answers; and two wills by Sylvia Llewelyn Davies, dating from 1907 and 1910, and Barrie's controversial transcription of the revised will, in which he appears to have substituted his name for that of Jenny Hodgson, sister to the boy's nanny, in order to secure his place as guardian to the five boys.
Oversize material, housed in boxes 9-10, contains material from Series II and Series III. Restricted Fragile Papers are housed in box 11.
Authors, English; Authors, Scottish; Dramatists, Scottish; English literature -- Scottish authors; English literature; England -- Social life and customs -- 19th century; England -- Social life and customs -- 20th Century; Photographic prints; Studio portraits; Authors; Dramatists; Barrie, J. M. (James Matthew), 1860-1937; Barrie, J. M. (James Matthew), 1860-1937 ( Peter and Wendy); Carrington, Dora de Houghton, 1893-1932; Davies, J. Llewelyn (John Llewelyn), 1826-1916; Du Maurier, Daphne, 1907-1989; Du Maurier, George, 1834-1896; Hodgson, Mary; James, Henry, 1843-1916; Llewelyn Davies, George, 1893-1915; Llewelyn Davies, John, 1894-1959; Llewelyn Davies, Michael, 1900-1921; Llewelyn Davies, Nicholas, 1903-1980; Llewelyn Davies, Peter, 1897-1960; Macnaghten, Hugh, 1862-1929; Senhouse, Roger, 1899-1970; Shaw, Bernard, 1856-1950; Llewelyn Davies family; Peter Pan, (Fictitious character)
- Correspondence, 1842-1963; Series I; 1.46; (4 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  Series I, Correspondence, is organized into four subseries: Outgoing Llewelyn Davies Family Correspondence, Incoming Llewelyn Davies Family Correspondence, Third Party Correspondence, and Llewelyn Davies Family Correspondence Compiled by Peter Llewelyn Davies.
  - OUTGOING LLEWELYN DAVIES FAMILY CORRESPONDENCE
    - Llewelyn Davies, Arthur
      - To Jack Llewelyn Davies, 1906 Jun 25 (Box 1, Folder 1)
        Envelope only
      - To Margaret Llewelyn Davies, 1903, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - To Michael Llewelyn Davies, 1906-07 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - To Peter Llewelyn Davies, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - To Llewelyn Davies vicarage, 1906 Sep 22 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - To Dolly [Ponsonby], 1905-06 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Llewelyn Davies, Crompton
      - To Emma du Maurier, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - To Mary [Hodgson?], 1921 May 22 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - To Arthur Llewelyn Davies, [1890 Mar 26] (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Llewelyn Davies, George
      - To J. M. Barrie, 1915, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Llewelyn Davies, Harry
      - To Arthur Llewelyn Davies, 1890 Mar 27 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - To "Meg", 1907 Apr 11 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Llewelyn Davies, John ("Jack")
      - To Mary Hodgson, 1901 Mar 17 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - To Peter Llewelyn Davies (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Llewelen Davies, Margaret
      - To Mary Hodgson, 1918, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - To Sylvia Llewelyn Davies, 1890 Mar 24 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Llewelyn Davies, Mary Crompton
      - To John Crompton, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - To Mary Hodgson, 1926-45 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - To Arthur Llewelyn Davies, 1890 Mar (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - To Sylvia Llewelyn Davies, 1890 Mar 25 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Llewelyn Davies, Maurice
      - To Arthur Llewelyn Davies, 1890 Mar 27 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Llewelyn Davies, Michael
      - To J. M. Barrie, 1917 Jul 2 (Box 1, Folder 22)
        Photocopy of letter
      - To R. H. Dundas, 1920-21, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - To Mary Hodgson, 1915-20, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - To George Llewelyn Davies, 1915 Mar 3 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - To "Gerrie" Llewelyn Davies, 1917 Sep 13 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - To Nicholas Llewelyn Davies, 1920 Oct 24 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - To "Jane", n.d. (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Llewelyn Davies, Nicholas
      - To J. M. Barrie, [1911]-24, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 29-30)
      - To George [du Maurier?], [1915] Feb 21 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - To Mary Hodgson, 1915-62, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 32-37)
        Includes photographs
      - To Eiluned "Bittie" Lewis, 1922 Sep 22 (Box 1, Folder 38)
      - To Sylvia Llewelyn Davies (Box 1, Folder 39)
      - To unidentified, 1916, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Llewelyn Davies, Peter
      - To J. M. Barrie, 1903-18 (Box 2, Folder 41-43)
      - To Mary Hodgson, 1917-54, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 44-45)
      - To Jack Llewelyn Davies, 1950 May 11 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - To Margaret Llewelyn Davies, [1913 Jun] (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Llewelyn Davies, Sylvia
      - To May du Maurier Coles, [1909] Aug 5 (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - To Emma du Maurier, 1885, 1890 (Box 2, Folder 49)
      - To Jenny Hodgson, 1910 Mar 24 (Box 2, Folder 50)
      - To Mary Llewelyn Davies, 1890 Apr 15 (Box 2, Folder 51)
      - To Michael Llewelyn Davies, 1906 Jun 16 (Box 2, Folder 52)
      - To Nicholas Llewelyn Davies, [1908-10?] (Box 2, Folder 53)
      - To Dolly [Ponsonby], [1904, 1907] (Box 2, Folder 54)
      - To unidentified, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Llewelyn Davies, Theodore
      - To Arthur Llewelyn Davies, [1890 Mar 25] (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - INCOMING LLEWELYN DAVIES FAMILY CORRESPONDENCE
    - Barrie, J. M. (James Matthew)
      - To George Llewelyn Davies, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 57)
      - To John Llewelyn Davies, 1906 Jun 10 (Box 2, Folder 58)
      - To Michael Llewelyn Davies, 1918 Mar 29 (Box 2, Folder 59)
      - To Nicholas Llewelyn Davies, 1918 Mar 21 (Box 2, Folder 60)
      - To Peter Llewelyn Davies, 1903, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 61)
      - To unidentified, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Du Maurier, George
      - To Arthur Llewelyn Davies, 1890 Mar (Box 2, Folder 63)
      - To Peter Llewelyn Davies, 1914 Dec 30 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Hodgson, Mary
      - To Nicholas Llewelyn Davies, 1946 Nov 22 (Box 2, Folder 65)
      - To Peter Llewelyn Davies, 1949 Apr 3 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Macnaghten, Hugh
      - To Arthur Llewelyn Davies, 1890 Mar 28 (Box 2, Folder 67)
      - To Sylvia Llewelyn Davies, 1907 Apr 24 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Others
      - Clough, Eleanor to Margaret Llewelyn Davies, [1907 Apr 25] (Box 2, Folder 69)
      - Crompton, John to Mary Crompton Llewelyn Davies, 1842-53 (Box 2, Folder 70)
      - Du Maurier, Daphne to Nicholas Llewelyn Davies, 1960, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 71)
      - Du Maurier, Emma to Michael Llewelyn Davies, 1914 Feb 3 (Box 2, Folder 72)
      - James, Henry to Sylvia Llewelyn Davies, 1888, 1890 (Box 2, Folder 73)
      - Lamont, L. M. to Peter Llewelyn Davies, 1949 Mar 25 (Box 2, Folder 74)
      - Nicholson, William to Nicholas Llewelyn Davies, 1937 Jun 24 (Box 2, Folder 75)
      - Rendall, Montague to Margaret Llewelyn Davies, 1907 Apr 25 (Box 2, Folder 76)
      - [Senhouse], Roger to Nicholas Llewelyn Davies, 1960 Apr 25 (Box 2, Folder 77)
      - Tennyson, Aubrey to Peter Llewelyn Davies, 1915 May 30 (Box 2, Folder 78)
      - Wilkinson, H. "Milky" to Peter Llewelyn Davies, 1910 Sep 14 (Box 2, Folder 79)
      - Telegrams to Nicholas Llewelyn Davies regarding his marriage, 1926 Jul 29 (Box 2, Folder 80)
      - ----, "George" to Peter Llewelyn Davies, 1938 Jun 19 (Box 2, Folder 81)
      - Unidentified to Nicholas Llewelyn Davies, 1937-79 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - TIHRD PARTY CORRESPONDENCE
    - Barrie, J. M. (James Matthew)
      - To Gwen du Maurier, 1910-20 (Box 2, Folder 83)
      - To [Robin] Dundas, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 84)
      - To Jenny [Hodgson], 1920 May 11 (Box 2, Folder 85)
      - To Mary Hodgson, 1918-25 (Box 2, Folder 86)
      - To Mrs. Hugh Lewis, 1914-25 (Box 2, Folder 87)
      - To Medina Lewis, 1915 Jun 13 (Box 2, Folder 88)
      - To Lady Northbourne, 1924 Jul 18 (Box 2, Folder 89)
      - To Dolly Ponsonby, 1910 Dec 4 (Box 2, Folder 90)
      - To unidentified, 1915, 1923 (Box 3, Folder 91)
        Includes photocopy
    - Du Maurier, George
      - To [Tom Armstrong?], 1899 Mar 26 (Box 3, Folder 92)
      - To Emma du Maurier, 1862-86 (Box 3, Folder 93)
      - To Mary Hodgson, 1910, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Du Maurier, Gerald
      - To Emma du Maurier, [1885?] (Box 3, Folder 95)
      - To Sylvia Llewelyn Davies, 1890 Mar 30 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Du Maurier, Guy
      - To Sylvia Llewelyn Davies, 1879, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 97)
      - To unidentified, [1890?] (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Hodgson, Mary
      - To Nancy Hodgson, 1912-20 (Box 3, Folder 99)
        Letters signed "Dadge"
      - To "Mother", 1912, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Others
      - Arnold, Allen to George du Maurier, 1885 Sep 9 (Box 3, Folder 101)
      - Booth, George M. to J. M. Barrie, 1931 Jan 5 (Box 3, Folder 102)
      - Cecil, Lionel to J. M. Barrie, 1922 Feb 2 (Box 3, Folder 103)
      - Coles, May du Maurier to Emma du Maurier, 1903-12, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 104)
      - Du Maurier, Emma to May du Maurier Coles, 1906-14 (Box 3, Folder 105)
      - Du Maurier, Trixie to May du Maurier Coles, 1909, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 106)
      - Great Britain. War Office to J. M. Barrie, 1915 Oct 27 (Box 3, Folder 107)
      - James, Henry to Emma du Maurier, 1910 Sep 11 (Box 3, Folder 108)
        Copy of letter
      - Jessel, Toynbee & Co. to unidentified, 1929 Jan 1 (Box 3, Folder 109)
      - Millais, John Everett, Sir to George du Maurier, 1890 Mar 28 (Box 3, Folder 110)
      - Roberts, Ellen to Mary Hodgson, 1918, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 111)
      - Others to Mary Hodgson, [1914?]-21 (Box 3, Folder 112)
      - Unidentified to J. M. Barrie, [1908 Mar 24?] (Box 3, Folder 113)
      - Unidentified to Lady Northbourne, 1926 Aug 11 (Box 3, Folder 114)
      - Unidentified, 1899, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - LLEWELYN DAVIES FAMILY CORRESPONDENCE COMPILED BY PETER LLEWELYN DAVIES
    - "Some Davies Letters & Papers continued, 1889-1907, compiled by P.D.," copies, holograph and typescript, corrected, with notes and annotations, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 116-121)
- Photographs, 1870-1937; Series II; 1.25; (3 boxes)
  Series II, Photographs, is organized into four subseries: Indexes and Albums, People, Places, and Other Subjects.
  - INDEXES AND ALBUMS
    - [Numeric Index to] "Lost Boys Photographic Collection" (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - "Photo Index in Chronological Order" (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - Empty photograph album with captions, n.d.
    - Empty photograph album with signature, n.d.
  - PEOPLE
    - Llewelyn Davies Family
      - Crompton, Mary Llewelyn Davies, [1888?] (Box 5, Folder 124)
      - Llewelyn Davies, Arthur, 1873-1904 (Box 5, Folder 125)
        Includes studio portraits by Henry Ashdown, Deneulain & Blake, and Frederick Hollyer
      - Llewelyn Davies family, [1888?]-1930 (Box 5, Folder 126-131)
      - Llewelyn Davies family at Drumnadrochit, Scotland, 1907 (Box 5, Folder 132-133)
      - Llewelyn Davies, George, 1895-1914 (Box 5, Folder 134-136)
      - Llewelyn Davies, Harry, [1894?] (Box 6, Folder 137)
        Studio portrait by R. L. Simpson
      - Llewelyn Davies, Jack, 1895-1919 (Box 6, Folder 138-139)
      - Llewelyn Davies, John, [1888?] (Box 6, Folder 140)
      - Llewelyn Davies, Margaret, [1897?] (Box 6, Folder 141)
      - Llewelyn Davies, Michael, 1901-20 (Box 6, Folder 142-143)
        Includes photograph of Sylvia Llewelyn Davies on verso and studio portraits by Lizzie Caswall Smith
      - Llewelyn Davies, Nicholas, 1904-22, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 144-145)
        Includes studio portraits by Lizzie Caswall Smith, the Marine Studio, and others
      - Llewelyn Davies, Peter, 1900-16 (Box 6, Folder 146)
        Includes studio portraits by Lizzie Caswall Smith
      - Llewelyn Davies, Sylvia, 1892-1910 (Box 6, Folder 147-150)
        Includes studio portrait by Hélène, Hampstead, and copy photocopy of painting by [Charles Furse]
        Related Archival Materials note
        See also: Llewelyn Davies, Michael, Box 6, folder 142
    - Llewelyn Davies Family with J. M. Barrie and Others
      - Llewelyn Davies family, 1904-28 (Box 6, Folder 151)
      - Llewelyn Davies, George, 1897-1912 (Box 6, Folder 152)
        With Hugh Macnaghten and others
      - Llewelyn Davies, Gerald, [1913?] (Box 6, Folder 153)
        With Bernard Shaw, John Drinkwater, and others
      - Llewelyn Davies, Jack with cadets, 1908 (Box 6, Folder 154)
      - Llewelyn Davies, Laura, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 155)
      - Llewelyn Davies, Mary, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 156)
      - Llewelyn Davies, Michael, 1912-20, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 157)
        Includes portrait by Lizzie Caswall Smith and photograph with Dora [de Houghton] Carrington and others
      - Llewelyn Davies, Nicholas, 1908-25, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 158)
        Includes photographs with Asquith and Lewis families
      - Llewelyn Davies, Sylvia, 1890-1905 (Box 7, Folder 159)
        Includes studio portrait by A. Debenham
    - Others
      - Ansell, Mary, 1892 (Box 7, Folder 160)
      - Barrie, J. M. (James Matthew), 1898-1933, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 161-162)
        Includes studio portrait, signed, to Sylvia Llewelyn Davies
      - Beaumont, Muriel, 1898 (Box 7, Folder 163)
        Studio portrait by Alfred Ellis & Walery
      - Chase, Pauline, 1906 (Box 7, Folder 164)
      - Coles, May du Maurier, 1895 (Box 7, Folder 165)
        Studio portrait by Elliott & Fry
      - Du Maurier, Emma, 1890, 1900 (Box 7, Folder 166)
      - Du Maurier family, 1874 (Box 7, Folder 167)
      - Du Maurier, George, [1888?]-92 (Box 7, Folder 168)
        Includes studio portrait by Fradelle & Young
      - Du Maurier, Gerald, 1898 (Box 7, Folder 169)
        Studio portrait by London Stereoscopic Company
        See also: Du Maurier, Guy, Box 7, folder 170
      - Du Maurier, Guy, 1890-1912 (Box 7, Folder 170)
        Includes studio portraits by Elliott & Fry
      - Du Maurier, Sylvia
        See: Llewelyn Davies, Sylvia, Box 6, folders 147-150
      - Hodgson, Mary, 1890-1916 (Box 7, Folder 171)
        Includes studio portraits by Geo. Hooper and Sutcliffe
      - Millar, Charles, [1890?] (Box 7, Folder 172)
        Studio portrait by F. M. Sutcliffe